It's a Lovely Life.
Crimes of Passion is a crime, drama, thriller film directed by Ken Russell.
Fashion designer Joanna Crane leads a double life.
By night she is China Blue, a prostitute who's attracted the attention of a sexually frustrated
private detective, and a psychopathic priest in possession of a murderous sex toy.
Joanna Crane / China Blue, played by Kathleen Turner.
Reverend Peter Shayne, played by Anthony Perkins.
Bobby Grady, played by John Laughlin.
Amy Grady, played by Annie Potts.
Donny Hopper, played by Bruce Davison.
Lou Bateman, played by Norman Burton.
Crimes of Passion is a 1984 American erotic thriller film directed by Ken Russell
and starring Kathleen Turner, Anthony Perkins, and John Laughlin.
The film explores themes of human relationships and mental illness.
A mix of sex and suspense, the film opened to controversy
over its content and to negative reviews.
The film explores themes of prostitute, double life,
detective, role playing, preacher.
The tone is emotional and intense.